tripsinsider.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Trips Insider

**Date of last effective update is** **22** , October, 2015.

Welcome to the website located at <http://www.tripsinsider.com/> (hereinafter, the “ **Site** ”), provided to you by Stingray Holdings LLC (hereinafter, “ **Trips Insider** ”, and also “ **we** ” and/or “ **us** ”).  Trips Insider provides and enforces this Privacy Policy (hereinafter referred to as the “ **Policy** ) to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use, treatment and disclosure of your personal data and other information we may receive from our users, vendors and/or partners.  For purposes of this Policy, the Site will be the initial contact between you and Trips Insider and will serve as initial point of collection of any personal data you may provide us.  Trips Insider is an travel information website — not a travel agency or travel service provider — where you will be able to receive certain services allowed by our platform’s functionalities, including but not limited to, travel service quotes, hotels, airfare, date, destination, number of travelers, price range; and thereby our database and search engine’s functionalities will provide you with multiple results and quotes from leading travel websites and tour providers.  You must carefully read this Policy and our applicable [Terms of Use](http://www.tripsinsider.com/terms-of-use/) (the “ **Terms** ”), incorporated herein by reference.

**_Scope_**

This Policy applies only to people who wish to use and receive our services. If you do not need or do not want to use our services, please close this web tab and exit our Site.  Trips Insider follows all legal requirements to protect your privacy. Our Policy is a legal statement that explains how we may collect information from you, how we may disclose your information, and how you can limit our disclosing of your information.

As used herein, the terms “ **use** ”, “ **collect** ”, “ **treat** ”, “ **process** ” and “ **disclose** ”, when related to personal information and other data, include use of cookies inside a computer, and statistical and analytical complication thereof for the creation of aggregate databases and marketing strategies; also including but not limiting, the storage, use, combination, integration, disclose, process and transfer of such personal information within our affiliated companies or other third parties in many countries.

**_Updates_**

If we make material changes to this policy, we may notify you on our Site, by a blog post, by email, or by any method we deem convenient, at our sole discretion.  We will also change the date of last update first shown above of this Policy.  We also reserve the right to update the Terms and/or the Site, at any time and without prior notice to you, and at our sole and final discretion.  Your continued use of the Site thereof after the effective date of modifications to the Policy, either by registration or simple use thereby indicates your acknowledgement of any modifications thereof.

**_Minors_**

Under the terms and conditions of the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, Trips Insider does not collect any kind of information from any person under the age of thirteen (13) years, and we do not knowingly collect or store any personal information about children under the age of thirteen (13).

Therefore, persons under the age of thirteen (13) may only use our service and access our Site under the direct supervision of an adult guardian or parent. We duly undertake the protection of minors and children, and thereby encourage parents, legal guardians and adults to be actively involved in helping minors under their custody to learn about the safe use of the Internet.  We recommend that you browse the following websites, among others, to learn more about current providers of children protection services: [www.cybersitter.com](http://www.cybersitter.com/), [www.securitysoft.com](http://www.securitysoft.com/) and [www.surfcontrol.com](http://www.surfcontrol.com/).   If you believe that we might have any personal information from or about a child under thirteen (13), please contact us at: <http://www.tripsinsider.com/contact-us>

**_Information collected, purpose and use_**

Generally, you control the amount and type of information you provide to us when using our Site.  As a visitor to our Site, you will be able to browse it without being required to register and/or provide us with any personally identifiable information of you.  In the future, we may provide the functionality to register into the Site and thereby create a personalized profile.   We may automatically receive certain non-personally identifiable from your web browser or mobile device; which includes the name of the website from which you entered our Site, if any, as well as the name of the website to which you’re headed when you leave our website.  This information also includes the IP address of your computer/proxy server that you use to access the Internet, your Internet provider name, web browser type, type of mobile device, and computer operating system.  We use all of this anonymized information to analyze trends and aggregate such data for internal analytic among our users to help improve our Site.

We may also collect certain personally identifiable information from you when you log in to our Site through the functionality of logging in and/or using your credentials with third party websites or applications (e.g. Google, Facebook, Twitter) in conjunction with the Site and, in such cases, we will not collect more information about you from these accounts beyond the personal information such third party service provider releases to us.  We may use Google Analytics to collect and process certain analytics data from your usage of our services. Google provides certain privacy options at [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).

We and/or our commercial partners may, in the future, request your email and mobile phone number from you, in order to contact you with our newsletters and to deliver you promotional materials and information which may be of interest to you, either by email or through Short Message services (“SMS”).  Under the CAN-SPAM Act, we offer free opt-out mechanisms in every commercial request we sent to our users.  If you decide – at any time – that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please use the unsubscribe instructions provided in any email or SMS communication you receive from us and/or our partners.

This Site uses the ClickTale customer experience analytics service, which helps us analyze how visitors use our Site.  We do not collect through the ClickTale service or transfer to ClickTale any personal identifiable information.  ClickTale does not create a user profile for the purpose of tracking a user across unrelated web sites and will only use such information pursuant to its Privacy Policy (currently located at <http://www.clicktale.com/privacy_service.aspx>).  You can choose to disable the ClickTale service by following the instructions located at <http://www.clicktale.net/disable.html>.

We do not currently collect any sensitive personal data about you, such as ethnic origin, political opinions and financial data like credit card or bank information.

**_Personal data o_** ** _wners’ rights and revocation of consent (ARCO Rights)_**

Any user of the Site has the right to make a request to us in order to uphold his rights to: (i) Access his personal data; (ii) Rectify his personal data when inaccurate or incomplete; (iii) Cancel his personal data; (iv) Object with legitimate reasons the process of his personal data; and (v) Revoke his consent for the process of his personal data at any moment, in order to stop its use.

The exercise of your rights to access, rectify or cancel your personal data and/or object or otherwise revoke your consent should be requested in writing to us and must include, at the least, the following information: (i) your name, address and e-mail address in order to notify you of the response to your request; (ii) documents establishing your identity; (iii) a clear and concise description of the personal data with regard to which you seek to uphold any of the abovementioned rights (when rectification is requested, modifications to be made should be specified and documentation provided to back up its request). For the exercise of your previous rights, Trips Insider hereby provides its users with the following e-contact form: <http://www.tripsinsider.com/contact-us/>. Upon your request to us, and after proper review, we may deactivate or delete your personal data and other information from our active databases. Please be advised that we may not be able to delete all of your personal data from some of our secure databases, and in such case we will make the data permanently inaccessible to any third parties.  You may also review or change the personal information we store about you at any time, by going to your account settings.

**_International transfer_**

Our Site is based in the United States of America (‘USA’) and, therefore is subject to USA applicable laws.  If you are accessing our Site from other jurisdictions, please be advised that you are transferring your personal information to us and, thus, by using our Site, you hereby consent to that transfer.  You may be accessing our Site or mobile applications from regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from those of the USA, and you can rest assured that we take industry-standard security measures to safeguard your personally identifiable information.

**_Cookies and beacons_**

Like many other websites, we use cookies to track and collect information about your use of our services. “Cookies” are small data files and identifiers that we transfer to your computer or device that allow us to recognize your browser or device and tell us how and when pages in our service are visited and by how many people. We link the information we store in cookies to the information you may have provided us while using the Site. We also use web beacons, tags and other means on our Site. Such beacons are an electronic file, sometimes only a pixel or small image, embedded on websites. While not designed to be visible to the naked eye, they nonetheless allow us to know the number of users who used certain portions of our Site and to generate aggregated statistics.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. If you wish so, you can easily disable cookies on your web browsing software by following the step-by-step guides located at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) and at [www.youronlinechoices.com](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/).

**_Information disclosure_**

We will not sell any of your information to third parties for marketing purpose, and we shall take commercially reasonable steps to maintain the security of such information. We use industry standard security measures to protect your information from unauthorized access, including secure hardware and software.  We may provide your personally identifiable information to affiliates that provide services to us with regards to our Site (i.e. payment processors, website hosting companies); and such affiliates will only receive information necessary to provide the respective services and will be bound by confidentiality agreements limiting the use and disclosure of such information.

We will also release any and all collected information and/or personal data under the following circumstances: (i) if required by applicable law; (ii) in response to a valid request from a law enforcement agency; (iii) at our sole and final discretion, to defend ourselves, our users and our affiliates from legal claims by third parties and to respond to such claims and legal processes (including takedown notices and subpoenas); (iv) to protect the property, rights and integrity of Trips Insider or any third party; and (v) to prevent or terminate any activity we may consider to be — or which me may consider to pose a risk — of any illegal, unethical or objectionable activity.   Otherwise, your personal data will not be disclosed to any third party, unless you provide your consent to such disclosure.

**_Links to other websites_**

Our Site may contain links to the websites of our commercial partners and other third parties that are not under our direct control. If you choose to visit such websites, we have no control of or responsibility for such linked websites and we provide these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors.  Such websites may place their own cookies and beacons on your computer or device.  Please remember that when you use a link to go from Trips Insider’s Site and/or mobile application or services to another website, our Terms and Policy are no longer in effect.  These third party websites are not subject to this Policy, and you should review the privacy policies, if any, of those individual websites to see how the operators of those third-party websites will utilize your personal information.  In addition, any banner or advertising of a third party we show on our Site and/or services does not constitute and endorsement thereof, nor indicates an affiliation with such third parties or their privacy policies.

**_Advertising opt-out_**

We may use Google Analytics and other software tools (like remarketing codes) from time-to-time to gather information about websites you browse view or when you undertake specific actions in a website.  This allows us to provide you a customized, targeted advertising for our users.  Therefore, third party vendors (such as Google, Inc.) may show you Trips Insider’ ads on certain websites across the Internet, even after you leave the Site.  Such vendors may use cookies and other web beacons to track your Internet browsing in order to serve ads based on your past visits to the Site.  Google Analytics is a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“ **Google** ”) which uses cookies to help us analyze how users use our Site.  The information generated therefrom will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers located in the United States.  Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage.  By using this Site, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set forth above.

If you do not wish to receive this type of advertising from us, now or in the future, you may opt-out by browsing the DoubleClick opt-out page currently located at [www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb) and following any instructions therein, or via the Network Advertising Initiative website currently located at [www.networkadvertising.org/choices](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices) and following any instructions therein.  You can also set preferences for how Google advertises to you by using the Google Ad Preferences page currently located at [www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/), and if you want so, you can learn about Ad Preferences by browsing [www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/) or even blocking some ads permanently by using a browser plug-in such as the one located at <http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/html/intl/en/plugin/>.  Our ads do not collect any sensitive personal data about you.

**_Takedown Notices, Claims of Infringement_**

If you believe that any content or other material provided through the Site allegedly infringes the intellectual property rights of you or of a third party, please notify us of your claim to <http://www.tripsinsider.com/contact-us/> (subject: “Takedown Request”).  The notification must contain the following information, at the least: (i) a signature and identification of the owner or the person authorized to act; (ii) a description of the copyrighted material that has allegedly been infringed; (iii) contact information, including your address and/or email address (in order for us to remit our response to you); and (iv) a statement indicating that the information provided in the notice is true and accurate.

**_Questions about us or this Policy_**

If you have any questions about our privacy practices or this Policy, please contact us at:

<http://www.tripsinsider.com/contact-us/>

Stingray Holdings LLC  
104 West 40th Street, 5th Floor  
New York, NY 10018  
United States of America
